<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>

<VV_Letter_ViviEggHatchedLabel>New Vivi Born</VV_Letter_ViviEggHatchedLabel>
<VV_Letter_ViviEggHatched>A new Vivi has hatched from an egg laid by {PARENT_labelShort}. Vivi grow and learn faster than typical humans but have shorter lifespans. They also inherit random genetic modifiers at birth, including those from their mother.
\nIf Vivi consume enough royal jelly during their growth stage, they develop into royal vivi, who live longer and can lay eggs. royal vivi have higher mental sensitivity and social skills but significantly lower work abilities and slower movement.</VV_Letter_ViviEggHatched>
<VV_Letter_ViviEggHatchedNoParent>A new Vivi has been born. Vivi grow and learn faster than typical humans but have shorter lifespans. They also inherit random genetic modifiers at birth, including those from their mother.
\nIf Vivi consume enough royal jelly during their growth stage, they develop into royal vivi, who live longer and can lay eggs. royal vivi have higher mental sensitivity and social skills but significantly lower work abilities and slower movement.</VV_Letter_ViviEggHatchedNoParent>

<VV_Letter_RoyalViviGrownLabel>New royal vivi: {PAWN_labelShort}</VV_Letter_RoyalViviGrownLabel>
<VV_Letter_RoyalViviGrown>{PAWN_labelShort} has consumed enough royal jelly to grow into a royal vivi.</VV_Letter_RoyalViviGrown>

<VV_Letter_IncidentHornetSwarmArrivedLabel>Titanic Hornet Swarm</VV_Letter_IncidentHornetSwarmArrivedLabel>
<VV_Letter_IncidentHornetSwarmArrived>A frenzied swarm of titanic hornets has appeared. They will roam around and attack any life forms they encounter. Titanic hornets are very fast and durable, difficult to take down with conventional weapons, but vulnerable to fire and poison.
\nThey cannot pass through doors, so hiding behind walls is safe. They will indiscriminately hunt the nearest targets, so it is advisable to hide if you lack adequate defenses. The swarm will hunt everything moving in the area and will leave on its own after a few days.</VV_Letter_IncidentHornetSwarmArrived>

<VV_Letter_LinkEverflowerLabel>Everflower Resonance</VV_Letter_LinkEverflowerLabel>
<VV_Letter_LinkEverflower>{PAWN_labelShort} is resonant with the Everflower, establishing a mental link. As the Everflower's attune rank rises, you gain various beneficial effects and can use the everflower's abilities.
\nThe everflower draws environment mana through the royal vivi, and the attune link strengthens whenever it absorbs mana or the resonant royal vivi performs an additional attunement ritual.</VV_Letter_LinkEverflower>

<VV_Letter_EverflowerAttumentLevelUpLabel>Attunement: {LEVEL} rank</VV_Letter_EverflowerAttumentLevelUpLabel>
<VV_Letter_EverflowerAttumentLevelUp>The everflower's attunement level has increased The following rituals are now available.</VV_Letter_EverflowerAttumentLevelUp>

<VV_Letter_FairyficationCompleteLabel>Fairyfication: {TARGET_nameDef}</VV_Letter_FairyficationCompleteLabel>
<VV_Letter_FairyficationComplete>{CASTER_nameDef} has fairyficated {TARGET_nameDef}. The fairyficated vivi shrinks to a tiny form and follows the royal vivi.
\nA fairy vivi does not experience time, has no needs, and cannot be attacked, but if the royal vivi dies it disperses and disappears.
\nThe fairy vivi usually does nothing but trail the royal vivi, though it may occasionally lend help.
\n\nA fairy vivi can be returned to its original form through the defairyfication ritual, but this leaves lingering after-effects and while they persist the vivi cannot be fairyficated again.</VV_Letter_FairyficationComplete>

<VV_Letter_IncidentHornetAssaultArrivedLabel>Titanic Hornet Swarm</VV_Letter_IncidentHornetAssaultArrivedLabel>
<VV_Letter_IncidentHornetAssaultArrived>A frenzied swarm of titanic hornets has appeared. They will roam around and attack any life forms they encounter. Titanic hornets are very fast and durable, difficult to take down with conventional weapons, but vulnerable to fire and poison.
\nThey are drawn by mana waves, exhibiting strong aggression. Unlike typical titanic hornet swarms, they will attack everything in sight until all living beings and structures are destroyed.</VV_Letter_IncidentHornetAssaultArrived>

</LanguageData>